A Finding Aid to the Millard Sheets Papers, 1907-1990, in the Archives of American Art AAA.sheemill
Archives of American Art
- Correspondence, 1929-1990, undated; Series 2; (boxes 2-4; 2.75 linear ft.)
  - Letters of condolence upon death of Millard Sheets, 1989, undated; (7 folders) (Box 3, Reel 5678)
  - "L" miscellaneous, 1943, 1965-1978, undated (Box 3, Reel 5678)
  - Mangskau, Connie, 1968 (Box 3, Reel 5678)
  - Manship, Paul, 1963, 1966 (Box 3, Reel 5678)
  - May, Cliff, 1964-1968, 1979 (Box 3, Reel 5678)
  - Maegen, Charles E., Jr. (Lubbock National Bank, Lubbock, Tex.), 1964-1968 (Box 3, Reel 5678)
  - "M" miscellaneous, 1929, 1960-1982, undated; (2 folders) (Box 3, Reel 5678-5679)
  - Newsweek, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Reel 5679)
  - Notre Dame, University of, 1965-1978 (Box 3, Reel 5679)
  - "N" miscellaneous, 1964-1979 (Box 3, Reel 5679)
  - O'Brien, William V. (O'Brien's Emporium, Scottsdale, Ariz.), 1960-1961 (Box 3, Reel 5679)
  - "O" miscellaneous, 1965-1979, undated (Box 3, Reel 5679)
  - Patrick, Andrew McIntosh, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Reel 5679)
  - Patterson, Sam, 1964-1966 (Box 3, Reel 5679)
  - Pollak, Frederick A., 1963-1964 (Box 3, Reel 5679)
  - "P" miscellaneous, 1956, 1960-1989, undated (Box 3, Reel 5679)
  - "Q" miscellaneous, 1965, 1975 (Box 4, Reel 5679)
  - Rheem Manufacturing Company, Chicago, Ill., 1965 (Box 4, Reel 5679)
  - Rockefeller for President committee, 1964 (Box 4, Reel 5679)
  - "R" miscellaneous, 1964-1978, undated (Box 4, Reel 5679)
  - Scott, Virginia Steele (see Series 4, Virginia Steele Scott Foundation, 1974-1978, undated), 1971 (Box 4, Reel 5679)
  - Sheets, Clifford, 1964-1966, undated (Box 4, Reel 5679)
  - Sheets, Mary Baskerville, wife, 1929; (2 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5679)
  - Sheets, Mary Baskerville, wife, 1942-1944, 1950-1972; (10 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5679)
  - Sheets, Mary Baskerville, wife, undated (Box 4, Reel 5679)
  - Sheridan, Ellen ( House & Garden), 1964 (Box 4, Reel 5679)
  - Small, George, regarding Ramos Martinez: His Life and Art, 1965-1975 (Box 4, Reel 5679)
  - Sotheby Park Bernet, New York, N.Y., 1976-1977 (Box 4, Reel 5679)
  - Southwest Museum, Los Angeles, Calif., 1964-1965 (Box 4, Reel 5680)
  - Stone, J. Ralph (Santa Rosa Saving & Loan Association, Santa Rosa, Calif.), 1963-1967 (Box 4, Reel 5680)
  - Swartburg, Robert B., 1956-1966 (Box 4, Reel 5680)
  - "S" miscellaneous, 1962-1979, undated; (2 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5680)
  - Tucson Chamber of Commerce, 1969 (Box 4, Reel 5680)
    (regarding San Xavier Mission)
  - Turner, Rufus L., 1963-1964, undated (Box 4, Reel 5680)
  - "T" miscellaneous, 1943, 1964-1979, undated (Box 4, Reel 5680)
  - Unidentified correspondents, 1965-1979, undated (Box 4, Reel 5680)
  - "U" miscellaneous, 1964-1975 (Box 4, Reel 5680)
  - Veale, Tinkham, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Reel 5680)
  - Villalon, Rene Patino ("Los Pretendientes"), 1970-1971 (Box 4, Reel 5680)
  - "V" miscellaneous, 1961-1973 (Box 4, Reel 5680)
  - "W" miscellaneous, 1964-1981, undated; (2 folders) (Box 4, Reel 5680)
  - "Y-Z" miscellaneous, 1966-1984, undated (Box 4, Reel 5680)
- Personal Business Records, 1933-1980, undated; Series 3; (boxes 5-6; 1.25 linear ft.)
  The files in this series reflect the personal business interests and records for Millard Sheets.
  The files have been grouped into three major subseries.
  3.1: Horse Files, 1939-1978, undated
  3.2: Financial Files, 1933-1980, undated
  3.3: Legal Material, 1932-1977, undated
  - Horse Files, 1939-1978, undated; 3.1
    This subseries documents the lifelong interest and involvement of Sheets with horses. Sheets actively raced and breed race horses for much of his life. Material within this subseries includes calendars for breeding and racing events, correspondence with professional horse organizations and breeders, invoices, charts, racing programs, tax records, and miscellaneous related background information.
    Files within this subseries have been predominantly arranged by document type. Within the Correspondence and Horse sections, folders have been further arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent or horse, respectively. Documents within folders headings have been arranged chronologically.
    - Calendars, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
    - Correspondence (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - American Saddle Breeders Association, 1939-1949 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - California Horse Racing Board, 1956-1963 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - Camino Terminado Farm, 1959-1961 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - Circle T Ranch, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - Miscellaneous, 1947-1963, undated (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - Jockey Club, 1958-1966, 1976 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - McMicken, Kenneth B., 1947 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - Rhoman Stables, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - Southwestern Walking Horse Breeders' Association, 1957 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - Thomas Thoroughbred Farms, 1959-1961 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - Upland Feed & Fuel Company, 1960-1962 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
    - Fees (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - Boarding and breeding fees, 1947-1969, undated (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - Jockey and trainer fees, 1954-1965 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - Shoeing fees, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - Veterinary fees, 1959-1977; (2 folders) (Box 5, Reel 5680)
    - Hauling, 1958-1961 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
    - Horses (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - "Anngeline Todd,", 1958-1961 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - "Bug Bomb,", 1960-1965 (Box 5, Reel 5680)
      - "Hemet Princess,", 1957-1965, undated (Box 5, Reel 5680-5681)
      - "Moolah Lady,", 1962-1964 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - "Neapolitano Presciana IV,", 1960-1963 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - "Rebel Defense,", 1957-1965, undated (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - "Red Step" and "Steponaway,", 1939, 1953-1960, undated (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - "Roxy,", 1966-1968, undated (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - "Secret Sunlight,", 1958-1960 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - "Skipper Roan,", 1960-1962 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - "Sturdy Defense,", 1947-1956 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - "Supreme Host,", 1963-1967, undated (Box 5, Reel 5681)
    - Income and tax information, 1956-1966, undated (Box 5, Reel 5681)
    - Miscellany, 1940-1967 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
    - Pedigree charts, 1944-1970, undated (Box 5, Reel 5681)
    - Photographs (see Series 13, Horses, 1934-1975, undated) (Box 5, Reel 5681)
    - Racing programs, 1957-1967 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
    - Scorpion II Syndicate, 1958-1963 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
  - Financial Material, 1933-1980, undated; 3.2
    This subseries consists of a variety of materials such as receipts, expense sheets, financial reports, income tax returns, insurance policies, inventories, and miscellaneous correspondence relating to Sheets's personal financial affairs.
    The files are arranged alphabetically by document type. Within folder headings, the material is arranged chronologically.
    - Checkbook stubs, 1960 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
    - Donations, 1958-1980 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
    - Estate planning reports, 1966-1972, undated (Box 5, Reel 5681)
    - Expenditures sheets, 1969, 1973-1980 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
    - Financial statements, 1961 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
    - Income tax returns, 1957-1962 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
    - Insurance Policies (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - Canada Life Assurance Company, 1933-1980, undated (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - Los Angeles Times Subscriber Insurance, 1938-1977, undated (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - Miscellaneous policies, 1933-1976, undated (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - Mutual Benefit Life Insurance Company, 1959-1977 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - Mutual of Omaha Insurance Company, 1972-1977 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - Pick and Biederman Insurance, 1969-1978 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - R. N. Loucks & Son Insurance, 1934-1937 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - Rose, Thomson, Young & Company, Ltd., 1965 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
      - Sovereign Life Insurance Company of California, 1972-1977 (Box 5, Reel 5681)
    - Personal property inventories, 1960-1965, undated (Box 6, Reel 5681)
    - Real Estate (Box 6, Reel 5681)
      - Claremont, Calif. residence, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Reel 5681)
      - Gualala, Calif. residence ("Barking Rocks"), 1962-1969, undated; (2 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5681)
      - Real Estate, Pasadena, Calif. rental apartment, 1969-1977, undated (Box 6, Reel 5681)
    - Stocks and bonds, 1960-1979; (2 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5681)
  - Legal material, 1932-1977, undated; 3.3
    This subseries consists of materials such as contracts, deeds, and miscellaneous correspondence, notes, and background information involving legal transactions.
    The files are arranged by document type. Within individual folders the material is arranged chronologically.
    - Car contracts, 1938-1940, 1963 (Box 6, Reel 5681)
    - Deeds, 1932-1936, 1960 (Box 6, Reel 5681-5682)
    - Loan to John A. Sheets, 1966 (Box 6, Reel 5682)
- Membership Files, 1946-1982, undated; Series 4; (boxes 6-8; 2.5 linear ft.)
  The files in this series document the wide breadth of Millard Sheets's interest and involvement in art, business, and educational institutions and community groups. He served as a board of trustee for numerous organizations, such as the California Institute of the Arts, the Claremont Colleges, Goodwill Industries of Southern California, the Otis Art Institute, and the Virginia Steele Scott Foundation. He participated as an active member in many clubs and professional associations, such as the Bohemian Club, the Economic Roundtable, National Academy of Design, Rancheros Visitadores, the San Diego Watercolor Society, and the West Coast Watercolor Society.
  The material in this section is arranged alphabetically by name of organization and then ordered chronologically within each folder.
  - All Nations Fair, Board of Directors, 1964 (Box 6, Reel 5682)
  - Allen Nevins Memorial Fund, Board of Directors, 1971-1973, undated (Box 6, Reel 5682)
  - American Council of Learned Societies, Pacific Spectator, Editorial Board of, 1946-1949 (Box 6, Reel 5682)
  - American Watercolor Society, 1953-1982, undated (Box 6, Reel 5682)
  - Art Center College of Design, Executive Board, 1976-1981 (Box 6, Reel 5682)
  - Bohemian Club, San Francisco, Calif. (see also Series 6, Crow's Nest Camp, Bohemian Grove, Calif., 1968-1969), 1964-1978; (5 folders) (Box 6, Reel 5682)
  - California Institute of the Arts, Board of Trustees, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Reel 5682)
  - California Watercolor Society (see Series 4, National Watercolor Society, 1966-1980) (Box 6, Reel 5682)
  - California World's Fair, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Reel 5682)
  - Claremont Colleges, Board of Trustees (Scripps College) (Box 6, Reel 5682)
    - Buildings and Grounds Committee, 1978-1981 (Box 6, Reel 5682)
    - Challenge Campaign Cabinet, 1964-1967, undated (Box 6, Reel 5683)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1982, undated (Box 6, Reel 5683)
    - Development Committee, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Reel 5683)
    - Financial Reports, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Reel 5683)
    - Invitations, 1978-1981 (Box 6, Reel 5683)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1966-1968, 1978-1979 (Box 6, Reel 5683)
  - Economic Roundtable, 1964-1980, undated; (4 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5683)
  - Girls' Collegiate School, Board of Trustees, 1964-1967, undated (Box 7, Reel 5683)
  - Goodwill Industries of Southern California, Board of Governors (see also Series 6, Goodwill Industries of Southern California, Los Angeles, Calif., 1973-1975), 1971-1981, undated; (2 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5683)
  - Historical Society of Pomona Valley, 1967-1981 (Box 7, Reel 5683)
  - Honorable Order of Kentucky Colonels, 1973-1975 (Box 7, Reel 5683)
  - International Platform Association, 1973-1977 (Box 7, Reel 5683)
  - Miscellaneous organizations, 1965-1979 (Box 7, Reel 5683-5684)
  - National Academy of Design, 1964-1982, undated; (3 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5684)
  - National Watercolor Society, 1966-1980; (2 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5684)
  - New Mexico Watercolor Society, 1975-1981, undated (Box 7, Reel 5684)
  - Otis Art Institute, Board of Governors, 1964-1967 (Box 7, Reel 5684)
  - Padua Institute, Board of Trustees, 1970-1977, undated; (2 folders) (Box 7, Reel 5684-5685)
  - Pasadena Hall of Science, Board of Trustees, 1975-1977 (Box 7, Reel 5685)
  - Rancheros Visitadores, Santa Barbara, Calif., 1968-1977, undated.; (2 folders) (Box 8, Reel 5685)
  - San Diego Watercolor Society, 1969-1982; (2 folders) (Box 8, Reel 5685)
  - Society of Motion Picture Art Directors, 1965 (Box 8, Reel 5685)
  - Studio Art Centers International, Board of Advisors, 1976-1979 (Box 8, Reel 5685)
  - Virginia Steele Scott Foundation, Vice President, Board of Trustees (Box 8, Reel 5685)
    - Art Collection, Acquisitions and development, 1971-1978, undated; (2 folders) (Box 8, Reel 5685)
    - Art Collection, Catalog, 1975-1976, undated (Box 8, Reel 5685)
    - Art Collection, Inventory lists, 1974-1978, undated (Box 8, Reel 5685)
    - Articles of incorporation, 1974 (Box 8, Reel 5685)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1978, undated; (3 folders) (Box 8, Reel 5685)
    - Dedication of gallery, 1974 (Box 8, Reel 5685)
    - Financial material, 1975-1978, undated (Box 8, Reel 5685)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1975-1978; (5 folders) (Box 8, Reel 5686)
    - Notes, drawings, and miscellaneous background information, 1975-1977, undated (Box 8, Reel 5686)
    - Sheets, Millard, founding role of, 1975 (Box 8, Reel 5686)
    - Special use permit for foundation property, 1975, undated (Box 8, Reel 5686)
  - Watercolor West, 1972-1980, undated (Box 8, Reel 5686)
  - Webb School of California, 1964-1966 (Box 8, Reel 5686)
  - West Coast Watercolor Society, 1969-1980, undated (Box 8, Reel 5686)
- Millard Sheets & Associates Designs, Inc., 1934-1982, undated; Series 5; (boxes 8-9; 1.0 linear ft)
  The series files deal predominantly with administrative aspects of Millard Sheets's major incorporated company, Millard Sheets & Associates Designs. Of particular interest to researchers will be the folder, "Art and antiquities acquisitions for clients, 1960-1966, undated" that document his activities to find, select, and negotiate purchases of artwork and antiques by European and American artists for a select group of clients and acquaintances. The folder entitled, "California State Board of Architectural Examiners, 1968" deals mainly with Sheets's correspondence with state officials who were investigating charges that Sheets was performing architectural services without a license.
  The material in this section is arranged alphabetically by subject, and within each subject heading the documents are ordered chronologically.
  - Antoci, Mario J. (accountant), 1964-1964, undated (Box 8, Reel 5686)
  - Art and antiquities acquisitions for clients, 1960-1966, undated (Box 8, Reel 5686)
  - Calendar (copy for Mary Sheets), 1968-1978, undated (Box 8, Reel 5686)
  - California State Board of Architectural Examiners, 1968 (Box 8, Reel 5686)
  - Chronological copies, 1968-1973; (7 folders) (Box 9, Reel 5686-5687)
  - Contract with International Pipe & Ceramics Corp. (Interpace), 1969-1972 (Box 9, Reel 5687)
  - Contractors, Berven Carpets Corp., Fresno, Calif., 1965-1966 (Box 9, Reel 5687)
  - Contractors (Box 9, Reel 5687)
    - Clausen, W. B., 1977 (Box 9, Reel 5687)
    - Custom Business Interiors, Covina, Calif., 1970 (Box 9, Reel 5687)
    - Miscellaneous contractors, 1965-1969 (Box 9, Reel 5687)
    - Pinton Freres, Paris, France, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Reel 5687)
    - Van Dyver Furniture Manufacturing Co. (Miller Desk; see also Series 13, Van Dyver Witt Furniture Manufacturing Co., undated), 1934-1985, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
    - V'Soske, Los Angeles, Calif., 1959-1971, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
    - Wayne M. Withrow & Co., Los Angeles, Calif., 1963 (Box 9, Reel 5688)
    - The Woodworks (David Sheets), 1974-1977, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Copy of agreement between International Club Hotels, Inc. and Victor Gruen Associates International Projects, Inc., 1965 (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Employees, 1960-1965, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - J. P. Evans Store remodelling, 1977, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Lists, 1978, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Mail log, 1974-1978, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Manufacturer's catalogs, 1976-1978, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1968-1982, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Miscellany, 1965, 1972-1977, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Notes and drawings, 1959-1977, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Office Building (655 E. Foothill Blvd., Claremont, Calif.) (Box 9, Reel 5688)
    - Appraisal, 1961-1971, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
    - Correspondence regarding sale of building, 1966-1977, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
    - Capital improvements and maintenance costs, 1967-1971 (Box 9, Reel 5688)
    - Myers, William E., 1971-1978 (Box 9, Reel 5688)
    - Photographs (see also Series 13, Office building, Claremont, Calif., circa 1968) (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Ossipoff, Vladimir, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Resumes and letters of recommendation, 1963-1985, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Salary analysis, circa 1976 (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Smith, E., State Examiner, 1959 (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Telephone directing listing, 1974, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
- Project Files, 1956-1981, undated; Series 6; (boxes 9-18; 8.25 linear ft.)
  This series comprises the largest group within the Millard Sheets Papers and documents the design activities of Sheets and his design company. The projects vary in complexity from single family residential designs to downtown urban renewal projects. The scope of his designs include architectural concept drawings, interior floor plans and elevations, murals, and mosaics. Sheets used his design firm to promote and illustrate his philosophy that art should be incorporated into every aspect of daily living.
  The files in this series document his efforts to create public and private spaces that reflect the history and natural features and resources of the region in their interior and exterior design. Of special interest to researchers will be the folders for the Home Savings and Loan Association, the Capitol Mall Project of Sacramento, International Pipe & Ceramics Corporation (Interpace), National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception in the District of Columbia, the University of Notre Dame mural, and the Pomona City mall and redevelopment project. These files reflect some of the highlights of Sheets's career as a designer. His designs for the bank branches of the Home Savings and Loan Association, in particular, rendered the institution's buildings instantly recognizable to the general population, and became a type of California architectural icon.
  Files are arranged alphabetically by the name of the project. Within larger project headings, the material is then further grouped by document type. Folders are ordered chronologically.
  - Ahmanson, Howard F. (Box 9, Reel 5688)
    - Guest house, 1965 (Box 9, Reel 5688)
    - Mosaic tables, 1965 (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Ahmanson Memorial, 1968 (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Bank of America murals (Paul Williams, architect), Long Beach and Van Nuys, Calif., 1965, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Bert Stewart Memorial Fund, 1965 (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Beverly Wilshire Hotel mural, Beverly Hills, Calif., 1971-1974, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Buffums' Department Store, Pomona branch, Pomona, Calif., 1961-1963, undated (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - Bureau of Reclamation, US Department of the Interior, art program, 1969 (Box 9, Reel 5688)
  - California Masonic Memorial Temple, San Francisco, Calif., 1969-1971, undated; (2 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5688)
  - California Scottish Rite Memorial Temple, San Francisco, Calif. (Box 10, Reel 5688)
    - Correspondence, 1960-1973; (2 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5688-5689)
    - Job costs and billing statements, 1964-1965 (Box 10, Reel 5689)
    - Notes and miscellaneous background material, 1962-1964, 1972, undated (Box 10, Reel 5689)
  - Cannell & Chaffin, Los Angeles, Calif., 1968-1969 (Box 10, Reel 5689)
  - Capitol Mall Project, Redevelopment Agency of the City of Sacramento, Sacramento, Calif. (Box 10, Reel 5689)
    - Contracts, 1963-1966; (2 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5689)
    - Correspondence, 1962-1966, undated; (6 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5689)
    - Fee negotiations, 1963-1964, undated (Box 10, Reel 5689)
    - Hearings and reviews of developer proposals, 1963-1966; (2 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5689-5690)
    - Informational material for developers, 1962-1964, undated; (2 folders) (Box 10, Reel 5690)
    - Job costs and billing statements, 1962-1967, undated (Box 10, Reel 5690)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1959-1960 (Box 10, Reel 5690)
    - Minutes of meetings, 1961-1966; (4 folders) (Box 11, Reel 5690)
    - Notes, 1962-1966, undated (Box 11, Reel 5690)
    - Printed matter (see Series 12, Capitol Mall Project, Redevelopment Agency of the City of Sacramento, 1963-1973, undated) (Box 11, Reel 5690)
    - Proposals, 1963-1966, undated (Box 11, Reel 5690)
    - Reports, 1957-1965 (Box 11, Reel 5691)
    - Schedules and miscellaneous background material, 1962-1966, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
    - Stone-Sheets v. Tishman, 1966-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
    - Transmittals, 1963-1966, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Carnation Company, Los Angeles, Calif., 1964-1965, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Carson City Mall, Carson City, Nevada, 1965-1968, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Central California Federal Savings & Loan Association, Auburn, Calif., 1969 (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Chapman, Mr. & Mrs. Charles R., residence, 1969-1971, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Children's Home Society of California, Los Angeles, Calif., 1965 (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Church of the Brethren, La Verne, Calif., 1962-1964, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Community Memorial Hospital of San Buenaventura, Ventura, Calif., 1971-1975, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - County Seal, County of Los Angeles, Calif., 1967 (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Crow's Nest Camp, Bohemian Grove, Calif. (see also Series 4, Bohemian Club, San Francisco, Calif., 1964-1978), 1968-1969 (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Cruishank, Mrs. F. G., residence, 1963-1972, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Damman, Mr. & Mrs. Joseph, residence, 1968-1971, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Dixie College Fine Arts Center, St. George, Utah, 1970 (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Dorn, Mr. & Mrs. Warren M., residence, 1974 (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Dunbar, Mr. & Mrs. John R., residence, 1967-1969, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Expo `74 Commemorative Medallions, Funding Associates, N. Hollywood, Calif., 1973-1974 (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - "Family of Man" mural, Los Angeles City Hall Annex, Los Angeles, Calif. (Box 11, Reel 5691)
    - Contracts and proposal, 1968-1971 (Box 11, Reel 5691)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Reel 5691)
    - Job costs and billing statements, 1970-1972 (Box 11, Reel 5691)
    - Notes and architectural drawings, 1969-1972, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - First Church of Christ, Scientist, San Francisco, Calif., 1970-1972, 1977, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Fulton National Bank of Atlanta, Atlanta, Ga., 1966-1967, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Garrison Theater, Claremont Graduate School and University Center, Claremont, Calif., 1964-1976, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Goodwill Industries of Southern California, Los Angeles, Calif. (see also Series 4, Goodwill Industries of Southern California, Board of Governers, 1971-1981, undated), 1973-1975 (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Griswold's Old School House, Claremont, Calif. (see also Series 6, Hallet Development Corp., Claremont Project, Claremont, Calif., 1966), 1972 (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Hallet Development Corp., Claremont project, Claremont, Calif. (see also Series 6, Griswold's Old School House, Claremont, Calif., 1972), 1966 (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Hearthstone Insurance Company of Massachusetts, Brookline, Mass., 1969-1971, undated (Box 11, Reel 5691)
  - Hilton Rainbow Tower, Hilton Hawaiian Village, Honolulu, Hawaii, 1968-1969, 1975 (Box 11, Reel 5691)